Friends, it is said that you should
invest in good stocks,
invest in those stocks whose fundamentals are very
strong and which are
seen to give very good returns, such
stocks are Britannica.
Although Nifty
saw a huge decline in the last working day, the
Sensex started 265 points below 17500, everyone's
eyes were on the fourth minute, so the
settlement was happening, on which everyone's eyes were,
due to which the stock market also saw a
decline, but the way
Britannica showed a rise in the last working day,
this is a sign of a good stock, you do this
best in this topic, in which
you get good returns, among them is
that stock of Britannia, a Loris company,
if you are my regular reader, then I had done the
last video, at that time this
stock was running at ₹3000 and I had
asked you to invest in it because
this stock was found at its 52-week low,
currently if you see the pass year result of the stock,
then there are 74 likes in this topic.  I had made a
deposit of
₹21,100 in five years and the same is 4153, they have
stopped at around ₹700 straight away. Should one
invest in the stock at this level right now? This
stock is a very high range diet video
stop, it was available at ₹3000 four months ago, it is
available at around ₹700 at this time, so one should
avoid investing in it. How is
this topic feature going to be, we are going to discuss all this in
detail, stay tuned till the end of the video.
This red bike is being opened by this stock and 6th
sense, it is being
advised to buy, in which a
strong bikeathon can be seen, the
rest has been folded,
tomorrow by your address, you will see a
strong and equal Aishwarya by self-confidence,
overall this stock has been seen by 36 fans, that is, it is being
advised to buy, the
stock is still going to be very high by half an inch
because its weight is also said to be that  It is
hovering around ₹4000 and this stock is
still trading at ₹300. If you want to invest in
China for 5 years, then keep a long-term reminder tomorrow. If you want to invest in China for 5 years, then you
can pick the stock inside. But if you have
taken a short-term loan and want to invest for 6 to 10 months or eight
months, then
you should wait a bit because this
topic may see a slight correction. The
targets given for this topic are of ₹
3781. ICICI Direct has
given a target of ₹3781. Whereas Sher Khan has
given a target of ₹980 in this stock. You can see the stock price is ₹3765. I
use first aid. So, the
way this stock is fundamentally,
you may see this stock breaking this target in the coming days. Then the
target given within it is ₹4620. Its
medium strength is
₹930. The low target is being made ₹32. According to which the
stock is running right now,
if  If it fights, you will get a
price tag of medium on the bike, then
about four and a half likes or you will
get returns. Birds playlist of
fundamentals. This stock will give you a medium target. I
can see that it will come back soon. The low target has been set. There is
little hope of it reaching this low because the stock has already made its target
once and right now there is no
such news in the market
which would have affected the stock in fact
and the stock has seen a huge decline. If we talk about the
investors of this stock, then there are
two big investors in it, then
SBI group has a holding of about 1.6
percent.
Insurance Corporation of India has a
holding of 1.3 percent. These are the top
holders. If we talk about the stock's
June quarter results, then a
decline was seen in it. The
group of the company has seen a growth of six percent in revenue
and now a decline was seen in its
net income, any possible net profit
margin,
but the way the company results are, the revenue
seen is quite impressive, Rs
3521 crore.  It had earned better revenue than the last quarter
but there was a
decline in net profit. It had earned 331 crores.
Net profit was
less than the last quarter. Anil's share will be 1335 primary. It was
less than the last quarter but the
overall result of the company was in the posting
because the fundamentals of the company are very
strong. We will
see that peer pressure. 57.67 boiled cup sugar has been
taken, its 34.01 tab setup near different
but it has gone out by 1.5 drops. It
is 48.94 in the tractors page. Sector-15
9.23 advance 1.4 2% is seen. The
fundamentals of the company are seen to be very good, there is nothing
negative. It is a
Loris company. This stock is picked for the long term
and
this stock gives a good and excellent result.
Complete different is also very
attractive. The company tries to give different three to four times a year
and every time the different of the company is
seen to be very attractive. Then its
community  Talking about sentiment, a
good improvement has been seen in it, but the
financial trend of the company seems to be falling
because the kind of results that were expected in
June, the company did
not get that result. Although even 3 months ago,
you got to see a good period,
but the financial trend that it had 3 months ago was
-2, there was a further
decline in it, it was -10th, currently it is
-11th, it is expected
that the second to Tuesday can be
seen to be excellent, due to this you can
also see an improvement in the financial trend. If you
look at the results of the company, the fundamentals of the company are
also very strong, the
financial trend has also not decreased, it has increased a lot.
In the results of 2022, the company has seen a hike in its results. It
earned a little less profit, but the profit was very
high. The company earned a profit of 1.5 thousand crores,
revenue earned 14000 36
crores. The revenue of the company was again from last year,
but there was a slight decline in net profit,
but overall  The
profit of the company is very good due to
which the trend of the company is very good.
At present,
promoters have more than fifty percent stake in the stock.
Still, there is no cooling of any kind.
Saif, you have more than 1629
meetings. The device has
more than five percent of the building stock.
Indefiniti Holi has
reduced its ECO point percentage to more than five percent.
Bird's eye view of the developing Holi has been shed. In
such a stock, SBI Bluechip Fund has
invested more than five hundred ninety-nine crores. If we
talk about ICICI Prudential,
more than 326 crores have been invested in it.
This is from the top mutual funds which have
invested crores in it. If we
compare it with the current track market value mission, then it goes a
little bit there.
If you do not have a short-term view, then you
can avoid using it for a little while on this earth. If you have a long-term mindset, then
you can click on that level also. The company is
accused of very high batting addition and good
returns.  This stock gives out this
stock number 1 month more
return than Mithai person has been given more than 3 percent return in one day
in three days more than
9 percent return in 3 months
one up in 3 years more than this person
74 percent more return in Kidnap Pal was
seen a fall of 7 percent in one year it was
a good opportunity to invest in this stock
this talkies trisection is not about the mid point then there is a
green signal that is why
investment can be made at a very good level
this token does he showed no network there is no
reply of any kind in the company the
company is not in anyone else's SMHS hum
list if we talk about the different of the company then the
last date is
from the middle of 2022 recorded 56th address how to
share different varieties of before the
company's boxes came out this time the
useful shares were out and then it can go up to 2162
pressure sometimes the company has tweeted that
two to three four different of the company
come out in a year and every time the
treatment of the company is very attractive  It is
seen that if the accused is arrested, then it is
very impressive, the
return of the company is also very
excellent for 15 years and the
way the company is accused, the return of 59
cents has been seen, which used to give a growth return of 38 percent 35 years ago, much
more returns have been seen than that, if we
talk about forecasting in the company, then at this time 22% will be
seen in the stock
because it is a fundamental research
company, so you will see a good return on investing in this stock,
friends, this video is made only for your
knowledge park,
before investing in anyone else, definitely take the advice of your financial advisor,
friends, if you like the video then do let us
know by liking and commenting, friends,
thank you very much for watching the video.